Guide to the Computational Engineering Building (Duncan Hall) Construction records, 1981-2002 UA 366
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Drawings
  - Subseries A: Approved
    - Associated Permits, Applications, and Studies, 1993-1996 (Box 18, Folder data_value_missing_89c289d710a19f49e268b41ce1647d23)
    - Campus Tree Map, 1992, 11/30/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 1-5)
    - Graduate Research Library Location Plan (Approved For Building Permit), 6/1/1966 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 6-7)
    - Partial Topographic Survey, Rice University (Sheet 1 of 4), 7/19/1993 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 8)
    - Site Layout Plan, C1.00, 11/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 9)
    - Site Layout Plan, C1.00, 10/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 10)
    - Site Utility Relocation and Site Demolition Plan, C2.00, 11/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 11)
    - Site Utility Relocation and Site Demolition Plan, C2.00, 10/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 12)
    - Site Grading Plan, C3.00, 11/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 13)
    - Site Grading Plan, C3.00, 10/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 14)
    - Site Utility Plan, C4.00, 11/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 15)
    - Site Utility Plan, C4.00, 10/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 16)
    - Civil Details and General Notes, C5.00, 11/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 17)
    - Civil Details and General Notes, C5.00, 10/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 18)
    - Civil Details and General Notes, C5.01, 11/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 19)
    - Civil Details and General Notes, C5.01, 10/14/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 20)
    - Site Drainage Area Map, C6.00, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 21)
    - Site Drainage Area Map, C6.00, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 22)
    - Storm Sewer Calculations, C6.01, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 23)
    - Storm Sewer Calculations, C6.01, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 24)
    - General Notes, S1.01, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 25)
    - General Notes, S1.02, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 26)
    - General Notes, S1.03, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 27)
    - Column Key Plan, S2.01, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 28)
    - Floor 1, Floor Plan, S3.01, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 29)
    - Foundation, S4.01, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 30)
    - Foundation Typical Details, S4.02, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 31)
    - Floor 1 Details S4.03, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 32)
    - Floor 1 Details S4.04, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 33)
    - Column Schedule, S6.01, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 34)
    - Column Details, S6.02, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 35)
    - Beam Schedules Floor 1 and 2, S6.03, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 36)
    - Underfloor Plumbing Plan, M1.01, 11/29/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 37)
    - Underfloor Plumbing Plan, M1.01, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 38)
    - Mechanical and Plumbing Partial Plan, M2.01, 11/29/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 39)
    - Plumbing (Sanitary) Risers, M3.04, 11/29/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 40)
    - Plumbing (Sanitary) Risers, M3.04, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 41)
    - Underfloor Electrical Plan, E1.00, 10/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 42)
    - Mechanical and Plumbing Details, M4.02, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 1, Page 43)
  - Subseries B: Civil
    - Site Plan Layout, C1.00, 1/25/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 1)
    - Site Plan Layout, C1.00, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 2)
    - Site Utility Relocation and Site Demolition Plan, C2.00, 1/25/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 3)
    - Site Utility Relocation and Site Demolition Plan, C2.00, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 4)
    - Site Grading Plan, C3.00, 1/25/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 5)
    - Site Grading Plan, C3.00, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 6)
    - Site Utility Plan, C4.00, 1/25/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 7)
    - Site Utility Plan, C4.00, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 8)
    - Civil Details and General Notes, C5.00, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 9)
    - Civil Details and General Notes, C5.01, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 10)
    - Site Drainage Area Map, C6.00, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 11)
    - Storm Sewer Calculations, C6.01, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 12)
  - Subseries C: Architectural
    - A1
      - A1.01, Index to Drawings, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 13)
    - A2
      - A2.01, Site Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 14)
      - A2.01, Site Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 15)
      - A2.01, Site Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 16)
      - A2.02, Site Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 17)
      - A2.02, Site Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 18)
    - A4
      - A4.01, Building Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 1)
      - A4.01, Building Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 2)
      - A4.01, Building Elevations, 6/28/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 3)
      - A4.02, Building Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 4)
      - A4.02, Building Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 5)
      - A4.02, Elevations - Arcade, 3/11/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 6)
      - A4.03, Elevations - Arcade, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 7)
      - A4.03, Elevations - Arcade, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 8)
      - A4.04, Elevations - Arcade, 3/11/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 9)
      - A4.04, Elevations - Arcade, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 10)
      - A4.04, Elevations - Arcade, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 11)
    - A3
      - A3.01, Floor 1 Floor Plan, 4/30/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 19)
      - A3.02, Floor 2 Floor Plan, 5/29/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 20)
      - Access Control, 7/30/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 21)
      - A3.03, Floor 3 Floor Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 22)
      - A3.03, Floor 3 Floor Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 23)
      - A3.03, Floor 3 Floor Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 24)
      - A3.04, Floor 4 Floor Plan, 5/29/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 25)
      - Access Control, 7/30/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 26)
      - A3.04, Floor 4 Floor Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 27)
      - A3.04, Floor 4 Floor Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 28)
      - A3.04, Floor 4 Floor Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 29)
      - A3.05, Roof Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 30)
      - A3.11, Floor 1 Paving Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 31)
      - A3.11, Floor 1 Paving Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 32)
      - A3.15, Enlarged Auditorium Plans, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 33)
      - A3.15, Enlarged Auditorium Plans, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 34)
      - A3.16, Enlarged Lecture Hall Plans, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 35)
      - A3.16, Enlarged Lecture Hall Plans, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 36)
      - A3.16, Enlarged Lecture Hall Plans, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 37)
      - A3.17, Enlarged Plans Toilet Rooms, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 38)
      - A3.17, Enlarged Plans Toilet Rooms, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 39)
      - A3.17, Enlarged Plans Toilet Rooms, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 40)
      - A3.18, Enlarged Plans Toilet Rooms, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 41)
      - A3.19, Enlarged Stair Plans, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 42)
      - A3.19, Enlarged Stair Plans, 1/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 43)
      - A3.19, Enlarged Stair Plans, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 44)
      - A3.21, Floor 1 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 45)
      - A3.21, Floor 1 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 46)
      - A3.21, Floor 1 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 47)
      - A3.22, Floor 2 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 48)
      - A3.22, Floor 2 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 49)
      - A3.22, Floor 2 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 50)
      - A3.23, Floor 3 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 51)
      - A3.23, Floor 3 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 52)
      - A3.23, Floor 3 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 53)
      - A3.24, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 54)
      - A3.24, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 55)
      - A3.24, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 56)
      - A3.27, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 57)
      - A3.27, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 58)
      - A3.27, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 59)
      - A3.28, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 60)
      - A3.28, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 61)
      - A3.29, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 62)
      - A3.29, Floor 4 Reflected Ceiling Plan, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 2, Page 63)
    - A5
      - A5.01, Building Sections, 2/6/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 12)
      - A5.01, Building Sections, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 13)
      - A5.01, Building Sections, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 15)
      - A5.01, Building Sections, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 16)
      - A5.02, Building Section, 4/30/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 17)
      - A5.02, Building Section, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 18)
      - A5.02, Building Section, 1/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 19)
      - A5.02, Building Section, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 20)
      - A5.05, Enlarged Elevation and Section - S. Portico, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 21)
      - A5.05, Enlarged Elevation and Section - S. Portico, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 22)
      - A5.05, Enlarged Elevation and Section - S. Portico, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 23)
      - A5.05, Enlarged Elevation and Section - S. Portico, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 24)
      - A5.05.1, Enlarged Elevation and Section - S. Portico, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 25)
      - A5.06, Enlarged Elevation and Section - Arcade, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 26)
      - A5.06, Enlarged Elevation and Section - Arcade, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 27)
      - A5.07, Enlarged Elevation and Section - N.E. Corner, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 28)
      - A5.07, Enlarged Elevation and Section - N.E. Corner, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 29)
      - A5.07, Enlarged Elevation and Section - N.E. Corner, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 30)
      - A5.07, Enlarged Elevation and Section - N.E. Corner, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 31)
      - A5.08, Enlarged Elevation and Section - Lovett Entry, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 32)
      - A5.08, Enlarged Elevation and Section - Lovett Entry, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 33)
      - A5.08, Enlarged Elevation and Section - Lovett Entry, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 34)
      - A5.08.1, Round Column Glazed Brick Layout, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 35)
      - A5.09, Building Elevation and Section - NW. Corner, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 36)
      - A5.09, Building Elevation and Section - NW. Corner, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 37)
      - A5.09, Building Elevation and Section - NW. Corner, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 38)
      - A5.09, Building Elevation and Section - NW. Corner, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 39)
      - A5.10, Building Elevation and Section - SE. Corner, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 40)
      - A5.10, Building Elevation and Section - SE. Corner, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 41)
      - A5.10, Building Elevation and Section - SE. Corner, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 42)
      - A5.10, Building Elevation and Section - SE. Corner, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 3, Page 43)
      - A5.11, Building Elevation & Section - Typical, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 1)
      - A5.11, Building Elevation & Section - Typical, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 2)
      - A5.11, Building Elevation & Section - Typical, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 3)
      - A5.11, Building Elevation & Section - Typical, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 4)
      - A5.11, Building Elevation & Section - Lovett Entry, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 5)
      - A5.12, Building Elevation & Section - Lovett Entry, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 6)
      - A5.12, Building Elevation & Section - Lovett Entry, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 7)
      - A5.12, Building Elevation & Section - Lovett Entry, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 8)
      - A5.13, Building Elevation & Section - South Courtyard Looking East, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 9)
      - A5.13, Building Elevation & Section - South Courtyard Looking East, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 10)
      - A5.13, Building Elevation & Section - South Courtyard Looking East, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 11)
      - A5.13, Building Elevation & Section - South Courtyard Looking East, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 12)
      - A5.14, Building Elevation & Section - NE. Corner, 11/17/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 13)
      - A5.14, Building Elevation & Section - NE. Corner, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 14)
      - A5.14, Building Elevation & Section - NE. Corner, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 15)
      - A5.14, Building Elevation & Section - NE. Corner, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 16)
      - A5.15, Enlarged Elevation and Section Balconies, 3/11/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 17)
      - A5.15, Enlarged Elevation and Section Balconies, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 18)
      - A5.15, Enlarged Elevation and Section Balconies, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 19)
      - A5.16, Enlarged Elevation and Section Balconies, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 20)
      - A5.16, Enlarged Elevation and Section Balconies, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 21)
      - A5.17, Enlarged Elevations Arcade, 3/11/1996 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 22)
      - A5.17, Enlarged Elevations Arcade, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 23)
      - A5.17, Enlarged Elevations Arcade, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 24)
      - A5.17, Enlarged Elevations Arcade, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 25)
      - A5.18, Enlarged Elevations and Section Balconies, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 26)
      - A5.18, Enlarged Elevations and Section Balconies, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 27)
      - A5.20, Wall Sections, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 28)
      - A5.20, Wall Sections, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 29)
      - A5.21, Wall Sections, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 30)
      - A5.21, Wall Sections, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 31)
      - A5.22, Wall Sections, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 32)
      - A5.22, Wall Sections, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 33)
      - A5.23, Wall Sections, 1/28/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 34)
      - A5.23, Wall Sections, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 35)
      - A5.23, Wall Sections, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 176, Folder 4, Page 36)
    - A6
      - A6.01, Exterior Plan Details, 3/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 1)
      - A6.01, Exterior Plan Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 2)
      - A6.01, Exterior Plan Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 3)
      - A6.02, Exterior Plan Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 4)
      - A6.03, Exterior Plan Details, 11/10/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 5)
      - A6.03, Exterior Plan Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 6)
      - A6.03, Exterior Plan Details, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 7)
      - A6.04, Exterior Plan Details, 3/11/1996 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 8)
      - A6.04, Exterior Plan Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 9)
      - A6.04, Exterior Plan Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 10)
      - A6.05, Exterior Plan Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 11)
      - A6.05, Exterior Plan Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 12)
      - A6.06, Exterior Plan Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 13)
      - A6.10, Exterior Plan Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 14)
      - A6.11, Exterior Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 15)
      - A6.11, Exterior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 16)
      - A6.15, Exterior Details, 4/30/1996 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 17)
      - A6.15, Exterior Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 18)
      - A6.15, Exterior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 19)
      - A6.20, Exterior Window Details, 6/28/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 20)
      - A6.20, Exterior Window Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 21)
      - A6.20, Exterior Window Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 22)
      - A6.20, Exterior Window Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 23)
      - A6.21, Exterior Window Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 24)
      - A6.21, Exterior Window Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 25)
      - A6.22, Exterior Window Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 26)
      - A6.22, Exterior Window Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 27)
      - A6.22, Exterior Window Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 29)
      - A6.23, Exterior Details, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 30)
      - A6.23, Exterior Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 31)
      - A6.23, Exterior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 32)
      - A6.24, Building Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 33)
      - A6.25, Building Elevations, 7/28/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 34)
      - A6.25, Building Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 35)
      - A6.25, Building Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 36)
      - A6.30, Exterior Roof and Skylight Details, 4/19/1996 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 37)
      - A6.30, Exterior Roof and Skylight Details, 3/28/1996 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 38)
      - A6.30, Exterior Roof and Skylight Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 39)
      - A6.30, Exterior Roof and Skylight Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 40)
      - A6.31, Exterior Roof and Balcony Details, 6/28/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 41)
      - A6.31, Exterior Roof and Balcony Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 42)
      - A6.31, Exterior Roof and Balcony Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 43)
    - A7
      - A7.01, Enclosed Stair Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 44)
      - A7.01, Enclosed Stair Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 45)
      - A7.03, Elevator Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 46)
      - A7.03, Elevator Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 47)
      - A7.05, Stair Sections, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 48)
      - A7.05, Stair Sections, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 49)
      - A7.06, Social Stair Sections, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 50)
      - A7.10, Social Stair Sections, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 1, Page 51)
    - A8
      - A8.01, Partition Schedule Finish Schedule, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 1)
      - A8.01, Partition Schedule Finish Schedule, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 2)
      - A8.01, Partition Schedule Finish Schedule, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 3)
      - A8.01.1, Partition Schedule, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 4)
      - A8.01.1, Partition Schedule, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 5)
      - A8.02, Paint Location Elevations, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 6)
      - A8.02, Paint Location Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 7)
      - A8.02, Paint Location Elevations, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 8)
      - A8.05, Door Details/ Door Schedule, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 9)
      - A8.05, Door Details/ Door Schedule, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 10)
      - A8.05, Door Details/ Door Schedule, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 11)
      - A8.06, Door Details/ Door Schedule, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 12)
      - A8.05, Specified Lever, 11/15/1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - A8.06, Door Details/ Door Schedule, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 13)
      - A8.07, Door Details, 11/15/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 14)
    - A9
      - A9.01, Interior Elevations, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 15)
      - A9.01, Interior Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 16)
      - A9.01, Interior Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 17)
      - A9.02, Interior Elevations, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 18)
      - A9.02, Interior Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 19)
      - A9.02, Interior Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 20)
      - A9.02, Interior Elevations, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 21)
      - A9.03, Interior Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 22)
      - A9.03, Interior Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 23)
      - A9.04, Interior Elevations, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 24)
      - A9.04, Interior Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 25)
      - A9.04, Interior Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 26)
      - A9.05, Interior Elevations, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 27)
      - A9.05, Interior Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 28)
      - A9.05, Interior Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 29)
      - A9.10, Interior Room Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 30)
      - A9.10, Interior Room Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 31)
      - A9.11, Interior Room Elevations, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 32)
      - A9.11, Interior Room Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 33)
      - A9.11, Interior Room Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 34)
      - A9.12, Interior Room Elevations, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 35)
      - A9.12, Interior Room Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 36)
      - A9.12, Interior Room Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 37)
      - A9.20, Toilet Room Elevations, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 38)
      - A9.20, Toilet Room Elevations, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 39)
      - A9.20, Toilet Room Elevations, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 40)
      - A9.30, Interior Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 41)
      - A9.30, Interior Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 42)
      - A9.30, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 2, Page 43)
      - A9.31, Interior Details, 2/1/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 1)
      - A9.31, Interior Details, 1/20/1995 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 2)
      - A9.31, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 3)
      - A9.32, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 4)
      - A9.33, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 5)
      - A9.34, Interior Details, 11/15/1994 (Drawer 177, Folder 3, Page 6)